<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>博客第一天 First day of the blog</title>
    <link href="/2025/10/18/BlogFirstDay/"/>
    <url>/2025/10/18/BlogFirstDay/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="博客第一天-First-day-of-the-blog"><a href="#博客第一天-First-day-of-the-blog" class="headerlink" title="博客第一天 First day of the blog"></a>博客第一天 First day of the blog</h1><p>你好，我是语深。今天是2025年10月18日，其实也只是一个再也平常不过的周六，一位平凡的工程师突然心血来潮创建了自己的个人博客。以前也在很多平台做过自己的知识分享账号，但是也都没有坚持太久。想来想去还是觉得得有自己的平台来分享自己的内容，这样也少了一些限制。作者始终坚信，较少的限制可以激发更自由的思考，从而进一步促进知识的繁荣和创新的涌现。同时有了自己的博客之后，将会有一片值得自己经营的土壤，在这片广袤的土地上自由的播种，并向所有人分享收获的果实，而作者也能在播种和耕耘的过程中得到自我价值的满足和提升。这片土地没有植被种类的限制，只要是作者认为能有所收获的都将慢慢播种和耕耘。也就是说，作者的博客将不会限制知识的类别和内容，只要是作者感兴趣的内容，在充分学习后将会更新在博客上。感谢各位读者的关注和支持，希望彼此都能在这片自由的土壤上野蛮生长，直到遇见更好的自己。</p><p>Hello, I am Yushen. Today is October 18, 2025, which is just an ordinary Saturday. On this day, an ordinary engineer suddenly felt inspired to create his own personal blog. He had previously shared knowledge on many platforms, but none of them lasted very long. After much consideration, he still felt the need to have his own platform to share his content, as it comes with fewer restrictions. The author firmly believes that fewer restrictions can encourage freer thinking, thereby further promoting the prosperity of knowledge and the emergence of innovation. Having his own blog also means having a piece of land worth cultivating, where he can freely sow seeds and share the fruits with everyone, while finding personal fulfillment and growth in the process of planting and nurturing. This land has no limits on the types of vegetation; anything the author believes is worthwhile will be gradually sown and nurtured. In other words, the author’s blog will not restrict the categories or content of knowledge; any topics the author is interested in will be updated on the blog after thorough study. Thank you to all readers for your attention and support. May we both grow wildly in this free soil until we meet a better version of ourselves.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>博客第一天</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>博客第一天</tag>
      
      <tag>Blog First Day</tag>
      
      <tag>创立日</tag>
      
      <tag>Founding Day</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>为作者点一杯咖啡 Buy the author a cup of coffee</title>
    <link href="/2025/10/18/Donate/"/>
    <url>/2025/10/18/Donate/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="为作者点一杯咖啡-Buy-the-author-a-cup-of-coffee"><a href="#为作者点一杯咖啡-Buy-the-author-a-cup-of-coffee" class="headerlink" title="为作者点一杯咖啡 Buy the author a cup of coffee"></a>为作者点一杯咖啡 Buy the author a cup of coffee</h1><h2 id="欢迎来到语深的个人博客，这里主要用于知识分享，如果您觉得内容不错，请在关于页为作者点一杯咖啡，非常感谢。同时如果有任何问题，请通过Github访问YushenFeb的主页来联系我。"><a href="#欢迎来到语深的个人博客，这里主要用于知识分享，如果您觉得内容不错，请在关于页为作者点一杯咖啡，非常感谢。同时如果有任何问题，请通过Github访问YushenFeb的主页来联系我。" class="headerlink" title="欢迎来到语深的个人博客，这里主要用于知识分享，如果您觉得内容不错，请在关于页为作者点一杯咖啡，非常感谢。同时如果有任何问题，请通过Github访问YushenFeb的主页来联系我。"></a>欢迎来到语深的个人博客，这里主要用于知识分享，如果您觉得内容不错，请在关于页为作者点一杯咖啡，非常感谢。同时如果有任何问题，请通过Github访问YushenFeb的主页来联系我。</h2><h2 id="Welcome-to-Yushen’s-personal-blog-This-blog-is-mainly-for-knowledge-sharing-If-you-find-the-content-helpful-please-buy-the-author-a-coffee-on-the-About-page-Thank-you-very-much-Also-if-you-have-any-questions-please-contact-me-through-YushenFeb’s-GitHub-page"><a href="#Welcome-to-Yushen’s-personal-blog-This-blog-is-mainly-for-knowledge-sharing-If-you-find-the-content-helpful-please-buy-the-author-a-coffee-on-the-About-page-Thank-you-very-much-Also-if-you-have-any-questions-please-contact-me-through-YushenFeb’s-GitHub-page" class="headerlink" title="Welcome to Yushen’s personal blog. This blog is mainly for knowledge sharing. If you find the content helpful, please buy the author a coffee on the About page. Thank you very much. Also, if you have any questions, please contact me through YushenFeb’s GitHub page."></a>Welcome to Yushen’s personal blog. This blog is mainly for knowledge sharing. If you find the content helpful, please buy the author a coffee on the About page. Thank you very much. Also, if you have any questions, please contact me through YushenFeb’s GitHub page.</h2><h2 id="微信赞赏码"><a href="#微信赞赏码" class="headerlink" title="微信赞赏码"></a><center>微信赞赏码</h2><img title="微信赞赏码" src="file:///C:/YushenFebBlog/myblogs/themes/fluid/source/img/WeChatDonate.png" alt="WeChatDonateQRCode" style="zoom:25%;" data-align="center"><h2 id="支付宝收款码"><a href="#支付宝收款码" class="headerlink" title="支付宝收款码"></a><center>支付宝收款码</h2><img title="AliPayQRCode" src="file:///C:/YushenFebBlog/myblogs/themes/fluid/source/img/AliPay.png" alt="支付宝收款码" style="zoom:25%;" data-align="center">]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>捐赠</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>捐赠</tag>
      
      <tag>Donate</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
